With the 82nd pick in the 2026 NFL
Draft, the Minnesota Vikings select
Dominique Orange, nose tackle, Iowa
State.
Well, he missed out on the marketing
opportunity getting drafted by the
Browns, but [music] he's a he's going to
be a good fit there. Orange is the new
purple. Oh, there you go. We could go
with that.
>> Come on now. I like it. We workshopped
it. He was dominant in the Iowa game,
the [music] rivalry game. Very powerful
guy. He plays that one tech nose in and
nose technique. He's going to be right
over the center and he can kind of
control the line of scrimmage and he'll
flash some of that lateral range, not
just pressing guys back, but you'll see
him [music] get lateral and make some
tackles. So,
interesting player. Pass rush, look,
there's no sacks. There's not a lot of
production to go off of there. [music]
You're drafting him to stop the run.
>> Well, they they also didn't ask him to
do that, right? Like that's the that
structure of defense was a 3-3-5
defense. This is This is why his
teammate, blanking on his name,
transferred to Texas A&M cuz they were
asked just two guys hold everybody up
and let those linebackers and DBs run.
It's part of the reason big citrus
didn't get his production
Him and Caleb Banks, they've added a lot
of beef. They certainly have.